

LEO GARDBERG

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT



+46 70 497 1022



Leo.gardberg@gmail.com



https://leoxd19.github.io/



Stockholm & Uppsala

PROFILE

Computer science student with international experience and a passion for innovation. I am excited to utilize technology to tackle modern challenges. Inspired by creativity, nature, and a perspective rooted in the arts and philosophy. Dedicated to advancing together with AI technologies to deliver impactful solutions.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

<u>SIGTUNASKOLAN HUMANISTISKA LÄROVERKET</u> (<u>(SSHL)</u>

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA NATURAL SCIENCE (ENG) 2015-2018

UPPSALA UNIVERSITY

PURSUING A B.SC. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE 2022-PRESENT

CAREER HISTORY

PLÅT PELLES CAFÉ

BARISTA & SERVER May 2018 – Aug 2018

WOOD PROPERTIES (SYNDEY, AUS)

LANDSCAPE ASSISTANT & IT SUPPORT

Feb 2019 – Jul 2019

SIGTUNAHÖJDEN HOTEL & CONFERENCE

SERVICE STAFF & BARTENDER

Aug 2018 – Oct 2019

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Python, JavaScript,
 SQL, Ruby, PHP.
- Frameworks & Tools: Node.js, Flask, Git,
 Matplotlib, OpenAl API (GPT-based tools).
- Al and ML: Proficiency in utilizing Large Language Models (LLMs) for workflow optimization and automation.
- Data Analysis & Visualization: Excel proficiency (pivot tables, visualization, automation).
- Customer Service & Technical Support: Skilled in delivering efficient, user-focused solutions.
- Troubleshooting, Software Installation & Configuration.
- Technical **Documentation**.

COMPLETED COURSES & MISC

- AI & Philosophy
- Programming Techniques
- Fundamental Information Systems
- Entrepreneurial Agreements & Responsibilities
- Administration 1
- Swedish drivers licence
- LANGUAGES: **Swedish**: Native. **English**: Fluent.
- PADI Certified Deep Water Diver
- I am happy to provide detailed insights into my practical experience and the tasks I undertook in my previous roles.